http://www.pion-inc.com/privacy-policy

DissolutionBiorelevant DissolutionBiphasic DissolutionDissolution AccessoriesCompendial DissolutionDissolution SoftwareSurface ImagingIn Vivo Predictive ToolsAbsorptionPermeabilitySolubilitySubcutaneousSurface ImagingPhysChem AnalysisIonizationLogP and LogDSolubilityDiscoveryPhysChem AnalysisSolubilityExcipientsPre-FormulationDissolutionSolubilityPhysChemFormulationDissolutionDissolution-AbsorptionOther assaysResourcesResource LibraryEventsTrainingBlogHome
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyWE UPDATED OUR PRIVACY POLICY EFFECTIVE JUNE 28, 2019PION INC. and its affiliated company, Pion Inc. (UK) Ltd, (collectively, “PION”) are committed to the protection of your personal information that is about you and which identifies you.  This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains how PION collects and uses personal information about you as part of our business activities, including information provided to us on websites, mobile sites, mobile applications, and other digital services and products controlled by PION that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, “PION Sites”). This Privacy Policy describes what personal information we collect, how we will use such personal information, who we may disclose it to and your rights and choices in relation to your personal information.  For purposes of data protection law, PION is the data controller in respect of the personal information that we collect and use as part of our business activities.This Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites linked from PION Sites.Table of ContentsThis Privacy Policy contains the following information:Information We CollectWebsite Use and Information We Collect OnlineHow We Use Your InformationHow Long We Keep Your InformationInformation We ShareYour Privacy Choices and RightsData SecurityAccessing Our Sites Globally; Transferring Your Information to the USChanges to Our Privacy PolicyHow to Contact Us With Privacy ConcernsInformation We CollectFor purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Data” or “personal information” means information that identifies you or that could reasonably be used to identify you. While some of the information PION collects is required for business engagement purposes, other information is voluntarily given by the individual.  The type of personal information that PION may collect, including through the PION Sites, may include, but is not limited to, the following:Contact information such as your name, address, phone number, or email addressRegistration information such as your username and passwordInformation about your employment such as employer name, title, address and contact informationEducation and other background information when you inquire about employment with PionPayment information (such as banking information, payment card number, expiration date, delivery address, and billing address)Content you may provide (for example, when you complete our Online Contact Form or submit other information)Details of products and services you have purchased from us or inquiries you have madePreference information, such as communications you receive from usAny other information relating to you (or other individuals) which you provide to us directly or indirectly through access and use of our Sites, by email or by phone, surveys or questionnaires, completing forms or contacting customer serviceWe may also collect personal information from third parties including your organization and representatives, public sources, our related companies, and other parties.Some countries consider some categories of information particularly sensitive or special.  We do not intentionally collect or maintain any sensitive information, including ethnicity, nationality, gender, religious beliefs, political opinions, health or genetic information.Website Use and Information We Collect OnlineThe types of Personal Data that we may collect while you use the PION Sites are described in this section and include both information that you provide to us and information that we collect automatically when you use the PION Sites.Information You ProvideYou do not have to register for a service or program to receive much of the information available through PION Sites. However, some of our content is available only to registered or identified users and will require you to set up a profile or provide specific information about yourself in order to provide you the service.Personal Data You Provide When Visiting PION SitesPION collects Personal Data that you provide on PION Sites, for example, when purchasing a product, to receive marketing products and information, contact PION customer service, or respond to PION questionnaires or surveys.Personal Data You Share During Other Interactions with PIONYou may contact PION to ask questions, discuss your concerns, or report issues regarding our products. If you communicate with or request information from PION, you may be prompted to provide your contact information as well as any Personal Data that is relevant to your request.Information That May Be Collected AutomaticallyWhen you use the PION Sites, we also may collect certain usage and device information automatically as described below.IP AddressWe may record the Internet Protocol (“IP”) address of your computer or other electronic device when you visit the PION Sites. An IP address identifies the electronic device you use to access the Sites, which allows us to maintain communication with your computer as you move about PION Sites and to customize content.Cookies and Other Tracking TechnologiesWe also collect information about your use of PION Sites through tracking technologies such as cookies and web beacons. A “cookie” is a unique numeric code that is transferred to your computer to track your interests and preferences and to recognize you as a return visitor. A “Web beacon” is a transparent graphic image placed on a Web site, e-mail or advertisement that enables the monitoring of things such as user activity and site traffic. These technologies help remember your preferences and allow us to bring you the content and features that are likely to be of greatest interest to you on the basis of “clickstream” data that shows your previous activities on PION Sites.We use Google Analytics to better understand our audience.  In connection with that we, and Google, may use third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) – and in some cases first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) – to inform, optimize and serve information provided on our website as well as potentially displaying ads across the Internet, based on a user’s past visits to PION Sites.We also may utilize Display Advertising (such as Retargeting with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting) to (1) show our ads based on your prior visits to PION Sites, and (2) better understand our ad impressions and use of ad services. In connection with the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting service, we may use data from interest-based advertising or third-party audience data (such as age, gender and interests) with Google Analytics to understand and improve our marketing campaigns and Site content.You can opt out of Google Ads by visiting https://www.google.com/ads/preferences. If you do not want your data used by Google Analytics, you can install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on at the Google Analytics opt-out page.Similarly, we may have LinkedIn tracking script running which serves advertisements based on activity on the PION Sites.We may work with new technologies in the future that require cookies or web beacons to provide their services. As we work with new technologies, their descriptions will be updated in the Privacy Policy.  This PION Site is not designed to respond to “do not track” signals received from browsers.To learn more about cookies and other tracking technologies, including how to disable them, please visit https://www.allaboutcookies.org/. Please note that some cookies are essential to the functioning of our Sites and deleting or disabling them will reduce the site’s functionality.Mobile TrackingPION Sites are available either as mobile applications or mobile sites that you can use on your mobile device. If you use a mobile device to access and use the PION Sites, we may collect the following mobile-specific information in addition to the other information described above: device or advertising ID, device type, hardware type, media access control (“MAC”) address, international mobile equipment identity (“IMEI”), the version of your mobile operating system, the platform used to access or download the PION Site (e.g., Apple, Google, Amazon, Windows), location information and usage information about your device and your use of the PION Sites.Information Collected from Other SourcesWe may combine information about you from a visit to one PION Site with information about you from visits to other PION Sites. We may also combine information about you that is collected through the PION Sites with information that we have collected offline, as well as with information provided to us by third parties, such as third-party list providers.As noted above, PION collects information from you in the course of your use of the PION Sites, products and services.  We collect information from you when you request products or services.  We collect information from you when you contact or communicate with us (including through the PION Sites, by email, phone or otherwise).  We also collect your personal information while monitoring the PION Sites, products and services.  We gather information about you when you provide it to us, or interact with us directly, for instance engaging with our staff.  We may also in certain cases collect or receive information about you from other sources.Other WebsitesPION Sites may contain links to other third-party websites that are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy.  These sites are not controlled by PION and PION is not responsible for any content on those sites or their privacy policies, which may differ from ours.How We Use Your InformationPION uses the information we collect for the following principal purposes:To provide you with the PION product and services you request and to respond to inquiries and communicate with you.To offer and provide information about similar and/or related products and services.To customize and improve your experience on PION Sites.To generally improve our products and PION Sites and other internal business purposes.Legal obligations to notify and report to authorities.To manage our business relationship with you, including for billing and collection purposes.Providing Products and Services You RequestIf you choose to purchase a product or receive our services, we use the Personal Data that you provide through PION Sites to manage your orders and invoices, to process payments, to respond to your questions, provide you the services you request and offer an optimal customer experience.MarketingYou may also receive marketing information from PION and related third parties, such as offers regarding PION related products or services, invitations to participate in surveys about our products, or notifications about special promotions. In such cases, we will use your contact and other Personal Data to send you marketing information.  You may opt-out of receiving marketing communications from PION at any time by using the opt-out options specified in our marketing communications or by contacting us as described in the “How to Contact Us” section below.Customized User ExperiencesThe Personal Data that you provide may be used to create customized offers, information, or services tailored to your interests and preferences. Also, we may use your IP address and the data that we obtain automatically through the use of cookies or similar tracking technologies to make our PION Sites easier to use and navigate as well as to personalize the content provided on PION Sites by anticipating the information and services that may be of interest to you.Business and Product ImprovementIn order to discover new facts that could help PION better understand customer needs and help improve, develop, and evaluate product, services, materials, and programs. PION analyzes the information that you have provided. For these purposes PION does not use information that can directly identify you.Site Analytics and ImprovementWe may use the information that you provide and the information we collect automatically about your use of the PION Sites to monitor user traffic patterns and preferences for site improvement, analytics and optimization.Legal Basis for ProcessingFor purposes of European data protection laws, PION has set out below the legal basis that we rely on to use your personal information. The legal basis that applies in a particular instance will depend on for which of the specific purposes described above PION is processing your personal information:Consent – In certain cases, PION may ask for your consent to collect and use your personal information. Should you choose to provide your consent, you may later withdraw your consent by contacting us as described in the “How to Contact Us” section below. If you have consented to a particular purpose for our use of your personal information, then we may rely on your consent until you withdraw it.  Please note that the withdrawal of consent will not affect processing that has already occurred, and may affect our ability to provide products, services or communications to you that are subject to the relevant consent.To Comply With Legal Obligations or for Performance of a Contract – In other instances, the use of your personal information may be necessary in order to comply with an applicable law or regulation or for the performance of a contract to which you are subject. You may not be able to opt-out of this use, or your choice to opt-out may impact our ability to perform a contractual obligation otherwise owed to you.Legitimate Business Interests – In still other instances, PION may use your personal information based on legitimate business interests of PION in communicating with you about our products and services, and about scientific research and educational opportunities. You have the right to opt-out of all such use of your personal information. You may do so by contacting us as described in the “How to Contact Us” section below.How Long We Keep InformationThe Personal Data we collect about you may be stored as long as it is required for the purposes identified when you provided the information for such specific purposes or for any new purposes identified by us and consented to by you, and for five years thereafter, after which point it will be archived only for so long as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out above, in accordance with applicable laws.Information We ShareWe only share your Personal Data with third parties as described below. We do not sell or rent Personal Data to third parties for their own marketing purposes.Third-Party Advertising and Online Behavioral AdvertisingYou may be provided with online advertisements of PION products and services on third-party websites and mobile services that are tailored to you, for example, on the basis of information that you provide to PION or a third-party website you are visiting, or of your browsing activity, purchases, or interests. These types of tailored online advertisements may come through several sources, such as the following:We may share with our advertising service providers your non-identifying information that we have obtained from cookies and other tracking technologies on our PION Sites.Some Web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to Web sites with which the browser communicates. As of the Effective Date of this Privacy Policy, an industry standard has not yet been established on how to respond to these signals. Therefore, PION does not currently respond to these signals.Third parties, Vendors and SuppliersWe have relationships with suppliers and affiliated companies, who help us operate our business and for whom it may be necessary to have access to your Personal Data in the course of providing services to PION. We may combine, share and exchange your Personal Data with our related affiliated companies in an effort to assist in managing and providing products and services to you. We will not authorize these parties to use your Personal Data for any purpose that is not related to PION and its related third parties business operations. We may also share your Personal Data with third parties to offer and provide information about affiliate products and services. We do not share Personal Data from countries that require consent, unless consent has been obtained in advance to sharing with related third parties. We require these third parties to handle your Personal Data collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and we will only share your Personal Data to the extent reasonably necessary to perform their functions.Co-Branded SitesWe may partner with other companies to provide you with content or services on a joint or “co-branded” basis. At a co-branded site, you will see both the PION logo and the logo of the co-branding partner displayed on your screen. You should read the individual privacy policies of our co-branding partners, as they may differ in some respects from ours. Reading these policies will help you to make an informed decision about whether to provide your information to a given site.Product ReportsIf you contact PION regarding your experience in using one of our products, we may use the information that you provide in submitting reports to the designated government regulatory authority, as required of us by law.Legal Rights and ObligationsIn certain limited circumstances, PION may need to disclose your Personal Data in order to comply with a legal obligation or demand, such as to comply with reporting obligations to our governing regulatory authorities regarding the safety of our products, including the U.S. Food and Drug Administration. In such instances, we will take measures to protect your Personal Data to the extent possible. We also reserve the right to use Personal Data to investigate and prosecute users who violate our rules or who engage in behavior that is illegal or harmful to others or to others’ property.Change in OrganizationIn the event PION decides to reorganize or divest our business through sale, merger, or acquisition, or in connection with the sale or transfer of one of our product lines or divisions, which includes the services provided through one or more of the PION Sites, PION may share Personal Data about you with actual or prospective purchasers. We will require any actual or prospective purchasers to treat this Personal Data in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.Children’s PrivacyPION does not knowingly collect or use any Personal Data directly from children on PION Sites (PION defines “children” as minors younger than 18). We do not knowingly allow children to order our products, to communicate with us, or to use any of our online services. If you are a parent and become aware that your child has provided us with information, please contact us using one of the methods specified below, and we will work with you to address this issue.For Individuals Located in the EU and European Economic Area – Your Privacy Choices and RightsThe European Union (EU)’s General Data Protection Regulation and other countries’ privacy laws provide certain rights for individuals.  Individuals located in the EU and the EU Economic Area (EEA) have certain rights, which may only apply in certain circumstances and are subject to certain exemptions.  You have the right to see and get a copy of Personal Data about you that we hold, subject to certain exemptions.  You have the right as to ask us to make corrections to inaccurate or incomplete Personal Data about you. You may have the right to receive data you have provided to us in a machine-readable format and to transmit that data to another controller in certain circumstances. You may also request the erasure of your Personal Data or the restriction of its processing, or object to the processing of Personal Data about you in certain circumstances and with certain exceptions.  You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where we rely on consent to use your Personal Data.  You have the right to complain to the relevant data protection authority where you think we have not used your Personal Data in accordance with data protection law.We may exercise our right to deny access to or correction of particular information in certain situations where permitted by law.  If we deny your request we will provide in writing the reason why it was denied.To seek access to Personal Data about you, to file a concern, complaint, or request for correction, or to opt-out of particular programs, please contact our Privacy Office by emailing us at privacy@pion-inc.com. You may also send a letter to the following address:PION INC.
Attn: Deren Dohoda
Privacy Office
10 Cook Street
Billerica, MA 01821
USAIn some instances, the applicable Data Protection Authority is responsible for making sure that privacy law is followed in your country. For more information about your privacy rights, or if you are not able to resolve a problem directly with us and wish to make a compliant, contact your applicable Data Protection Authority contact.In all communications to PION, please include your email address, the Web site address, mobile application, and/or the specific PION product to which you provided Personal Data (e.g., https://pion-inc.com), and a detailed explanation of your request. If you would like to delete, amend, or correct your Personal Data and are contacting us by email, please put “Deletion Request” or “Amendment/Correction Request” in the subject line of the email. We will respond to all reasonable requests in a timely manner and may need to further confirm your identity in order to process certain requests.Data SecurityPION maintains reasonable technical, administrative and physical controls to secure any Personal Data collected through the PION Sites. However, there is always some risk that an unauthorized third party could intercept an Internet transmission, or that someone will find a way to thwart our security systems. We urge you to exercise caution when transmitting Personal Data over the Internet, especially your financial-related information. PION cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will not gain access to your Personal Data; therefore, when submitting Personal Data to PION Sites, you must weigh both the benefits and the risks.Third Party Sites and Social Media Plug-insThis Privacy Policy does not apply to PION Sites that do not link to this Privacy Policy, or to third-party Web sites to which PION Sites may link. PION Sites may use social media plug-ins (e.g., the Facebook “Like” button, “Share to Twitter” button) to enable you to easily share information with others. When you visit PION Sites, the operator of the social plug-in can place a cookie on your computer or other electronic device that enables that operator to recognize individuals who have previously visited our Site. If you are logged into the social media Web site (e.g., Facebook, Twitter) while browsing on our PION Site, the social media plug-in allows that social media Web site to receive information that you have visited our PION Site. The social media plug-in also allows the social media Web site to share information about your activities on our PION Site with other users of their social media Web site. These sharing settings are managed by the social media Web site and governed by its privacy policy.Accessing Our Sites Globally; Transferring Your Information to the USThis site is owned and operated by PION in the United States, but the information you provide will be accessible to our third parties, vendors, and suppliers in other countries in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Furthermore, if you are visiting this site from a country other than the United States, your communication with us will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international borders. Where we transfer information outside the EEA, we will implement appropriate measures to ensure your Personal Data remains protected in accordance with applicable data protection laws. The level of legal protection for Personal Data is not the same in all countries and overseas entities may not be subject to laws that provide the same level of protection as your country; however, we will take the security measures described in this Privacy Policy in an effort to keep your information secure. By using this site, you understand that your Personal Data will be stored and processed in the United States and in any country to which we may transfer your information in the course of our business operations.  Please see the Section “Information We Share” for more detail on how the information may be shared with PION related entities and third parties.Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure.  Although we use reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee the security of information transmitted to our Sites and any transmission is at your own risk.  Once we have received your Personal Data, we will use reasonable and appropriate security measures to try to protect unauthorized access.Notice to California ResidentsSubject to certain limits under California Civil Code § 1798.83, California residents may ask us to provide them with (i) a list of certain categories of Personal Data that we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, and (ii) the identity of those third parties. To make this request, California residents may contact us at privacy@pion-inc.com.Changes to Our Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page with a new effective date. PION encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the PION Sites after we post changes is deemed to be acceptance to those changes.How to Contact Us with Privacy ConcernsTo seek access to Personal Data about you, to file a concern, complaint, or request for correction, or to opt-out of particular programs, please contact our Privacy Office by emailing us at privacy@pion-inc.com. You may also send a letter to the following address:PION INC.
Attn: Deren Dohoda
Privacy Office
10 Cook Street
Billerica, MA 01821
USAPION is committed to resolving your privacy concern and any complaint.  If you have a concern or complaint about privacy at PION, please contact us at the contact information provided. For more information about your privacy rights, or if you are not able to resolve a problem directly with us and wish to make a compliant, contact the applicable Data Protection Authority in your country.LegalTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyCookie PolicyClose
